Newland/Zeuner Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Instrumental Music (Box 5-23, Box 56-57)
  - Music for solo instruments (Box 5-20, Box 57)
    - Ensembles of 3 or more instruments - Printed music (Box 18-20)
      - Rode, Pierre
        - Air Varié pour le Violon avec accompagnment d'un second Violon, Alto et Basse par P. Rode. Oeuv. 10. Leipsic: Breitkopf & Härtel, n.d., Pl. no. 207. (Box 19)
      - Schmitt, Jacques
        - Variations Brillantes pour le Piano Forté avec accompagnement de deux Violons, Alto & Basse par Jacques Schmitt. Oeuvre 23. Offenbach s/M: J. André, n.d., Pl. no. 4835. (Box 19)
      - Steibelt, Daniel
        - Deux Sonates pour le Forte-Piano avec accompagnement de Violon et Basse (ad Libitum) composées par D. Steibelt. Oeuvre 33. Paris: B. Viguerie, n.d., Pl. no. 61. (Box 19)
        - Ouverture Turque pour le Clavecin ou Forté-Piano avec Violon et Violoncelle composée par Mr. Steibelt. Oeuvre 7me. Offenbach sur le Mein: J. André, [1893?]., Pl. no. 525. (Box 19)
        - Trois Sonates d'une difficulté progressive pour Piano-Forté, avec accompagnement de Violon et Violoncelle ad libitum, composées par D. Steibelt. Oeuvre 37. Seconde éd. Offenbach s/M: Jean André, n.d., Pl. no. 2231. (Box 19)
      - Sterkel, Johann Franz Xaver
        - III Sonates pour le Clavecin ou Piano Forte accompagnées d'un Violon et Basse. Composées par Mr. Sterkel. Oeuvre XVII. Liv. I. Mayence: Schott, n.d., basso part.; Pl. no. 18 (Box 20)
    - Ensembles of 3 or more instruments - Manuscripts (Box 20)
      - By Composer (Box 20)
        - Kuhlau, Friedrich
          - Quartetto, Op. 50, piano part (Box 20)
        - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus
          - Trio, B-flat clarinet part (Box 20)
      - Title only (Box 20)
        - [Unidentified], String Quartet, ? 1st mvmt. (Box 20)
        - [Unidentified], Trio for piano, violin, cello or viola? + viola? part (Box 20)
  - Orchestral music (Box 20-23, Box 56)
    - Concertos and other concert music - Printed music (Box 20)
      - Beethoven, Ludwig van
        - Adelaide von Beethoven. Zur gewöhnlichen Clavier Begleitung gesetzt von J. P. Heuschkel., Bassetthorn, Horn in F, Viola and Violoncello ou Fagotto parts; includes manuscript parts for Violin or Flute, an. Cornet or Clarinet in B-flat; Pl. no. 107. (Box 20)
      - Gyrowetz, Adalbert
        - Sinfonie Periodique Divers Instrumens composée par Mr. Adalberto Gyrowetz. Paris: Imbault, n.d., basso part - fragment.; Pl. no. 19. (Box 20)
      - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus
        - Concerto. Op. 4., Pl. no. 1556. (Box 20)
      - Rode, Pierre
        - Second Concerto pour le Violon, par P. Rode. Paris: Janet et Cotelle, n.d., Pl. no. 504. (Box 20)
      - Schmitt, Jacques
        - Var. No. 7., Pl. no. 3603.; Theme and Variations for Orchestra (Box 20)
      - Viotti, Giovanni Battista
        - Vingt deuxième [22nd] Concerto pour le Violon, accompagné de grand orchestre composé par J. B. Viotti. Offenbach s/M: J. André, [1805?]., Pl. no. 1841. (Box 20)
    - Concertos and other concert music - Manuscripts (Box 21)
      - Fantasie (Box 21)
      - Nel cor più - Solo for Clarinet in B-flat with Orchestra (Box 21)
      - [Unidentified], Solo Concerto - solo part not included (Box 21)
      - [Unidentified], Theme and Variations for Orchestra (Box 21)
    - Operatic overtures and potpourris - Printed music (Box 21, Box 56)
      - Bellini, Vincenzo
        - [La Sonnambula] Overture., violoncello part (Box 21)
      - Boieldieu, Adrien
        - [Caliphe von Bagdad] Overtura., Pl. no. 5538. (Box 21)
      - Cimarosa, Domenico
        - Matrimonio Segreto. Ouverture., Pl. no. O.S. 179. (Box 21)
      - Franzl, Ferdinand
        - Adolph and Clara. Overture (Box 56)
      - Hérold, Louis Joseph Ferdinand
        - Zampa. Ouverture., violino secondo part; Pl. no. 6040. (Box 21)
      - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus
        - [Die Zauberflöte] [Overture - flauto part] (Box 21)
      - Päer, Ferdinando
        - Sofonisbe. Overture de l'Opèra Sofonisbe pour 2 Violons, Alto, Violoncelle, Basse, Flute, 2 Clarinettes, 2 Hautbois, 2 Cors, 2 Bassons, 2 Trompettes et Timballes par Ferd. Paer. Mayence: B. Schott, n.d., Pl. no. 156. (Box 21)
    - Operatic overtures and potpourris - Manuscripts (Box 22)
      - Bellini, Vincenzo
        - Norma. Potpourri, string parts (Box 22)
        - La Sonnambula. Overture, orchestra parts (Box 22)
      - Boieldieu, Adrien
        - Caliphe de Bagdad. Overture (Box 22)
      - Cimarosa, Domenico
        - Il Matrimonio. Overture, orchestra parts (Box 22)
      - Donizetti, Gaetano
        - La Fille du Regiment. Overture, full score (Box 22)
      - Flotow, Friedrich von
        - [Alessandro] Stradella. Overture, viola part (Box 22)
      - Franzl, Ferdinand
        - Adolphe & Clara. Overture (Box 22)
      - Fry, William Henry
        - Leonora, title page only (Box 22)
      - Méhul, Etienne Nicolas
        - Joseph. Overture (Box 22)
      - Mercadente, Saverio
        - Elisa e Claudio. Overture (Box 22)
      - Rossini, Gioacchino
        - L'Inganno Felice. Overture (Box 22)
        - Semiramide. Overture (Box 22)
      - Verdi, Giuseppe
        - Ernani. Excerpts, misc. instrumental parts (Box 22)
      - Weber, Carl Maria von
        - Der Freischütz, violin part only; includes cast lists for London performances from 1821 through 1849 (Box 22)
      - Weigl, Joseph
        - Les Vestales. Overture (Box 22)
    - Popular dance forms - Printed music (Box 23)
      - Aulagnier, Antonin
        - Quadrille Deuriante par Aulagnier., Pl. no. 73. AA. (Box 23)
    - Popular dance forms - Manuscripts (Box 23)
      - By Composer (Box 23)
        - Donizetti, Gaetano
          - March from La Favorita see: Fry, Fill Up, Fill Up
        - Fry, William Henry
          - Fill Up, Fill Up, Includes: March from La Favorita (Box 23)
        - Graffula, Claudio S.
          - Col. Duryee's Quick Step [et al] (Box 23)
          - Oh would I were a boy again, also includes: Captain Shepherd's Quick Step by Graffula (Box 23)
        - Labitzky, Joseph
          - Elfen Waltz, also includes: Evening Star Waltz (Box 23)
          - Woronzow Waltzes (Box 23)
        - Newland, William Augustine
          - Villanova College Quick Step (Box 23)
        - Roland
          - Ladies Polka Quadrille [et al] (Box 23)
      - Title only (Box 23)
        - Hail Columbia [et al] (Box 23)
        - [Quadrilles] (Box 23)
        - [Miscellaneous instrumental parts to dance music] (Box 23)
    - Instrumental parts to orchestral works - Printed music (Box 23)
      - Beethoven, Ludwig van
        - Sonata [Op. 17] [Flauto o Violino, Corno in F], Pl. no. 2165. (Box 23)
    - Instrumental parts to orchestral works - Manuscripts (Box 23)
      - By Composer (Box 23)
        - Beethoven, Ludwig van
          - Concerto [Op. 15], violin part (Box 23)
        - Bohlman
          - La Sorcière des Ardennes, cello? part (Box 23)
      - Title only (Box 23)
        - Introduction - Maestoso Adagio, cornets and horn parts (Box 23)
        - [Miscellaneous instrumental parts] (Box 23)
- Vocal Music (Box 24-46, Box 56)
  - Sacred vocal music: Latin (Box 24-35)
    - Masses - Printed music (Box 24)
      - By Composer (Box 24)
        - Castegnier, A.
          - Agnus Dei par Mr. A. Castegnier. Paris: Journal des Demoiselles, 1858. (Box 24)
        - Concone, Joseph
          - Concone's Mass in F. Composed for 2 voices by J. Concone. Arranged for 4 voices by A. Andrews. [Kyrie] (Box 24)
        - Gounod, Charles
          - Gounod's Messe Solennelle (St. Cecilia) with Latin and English words, Edited, and the English words adapted, by W. H. Birch. London: Boosey & Co., n.d. (Box 24)
        - Greith, Carl
          - Responsoria ad Missam. In tono Solemni ad Voces aequales. (From the official Ratisbon edition.) Arranged and Harmonized by Carl Greith. (Box 24)
        - Haydn, Franz Joseph
          - Haydn's Mass No. 4. Novello's edition. [S.l.]: G. Andre & Co., n.d., Vocal and organ parts; Publisher information stamped; also includes manuscript parts (Box 24)
        - Heuberer, Charles F.
          - Festival Mass for Four Voices and Organ Accompaniment. Composed by Charles F. Heuberer. Boston: Charles F. Heuberer, n.d., Published and for sale by the composer. (Box 24)
        - Millard, Harrison
          - Mass In Bb for four voices, with organ or piano-forte accompaniment, Latin and English text, by Harrison Millard. New York: S. T. Gordon & Son, 1879. (Box 24)
        - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus
          - Twelfth Mass. No. 2 - Gloria in Excelsis. London: Boosey and Co., n.d., Boosey's Oratorio Choruses, No. 71; Magnificat arranged by W. C. Peters; also includes: See our oars with feathered spray, by John Stevenson (Box 24)
        - Vogler, Georg Joseph
          - Missa Solennis vom Abt. Vogler. No. 1. Partitur. Nach dem hinterlassenen Original Manuscript herausgegeben. Offenbach a/M: J. André, [182-]., Keyboard reduction added and signed by W. A. Newland.; Pl. no. 4713. (Box 24)
      - Title only (Box 24)
        - Missa de Angelis, vocal part (Box 24)
        - Sanctus (Box 24)
        - [Unidentified], Mass in chant form (Box 24)
    - Masses - Manuscripts (Box 24-29)
      - By Composer (Box 24-29)
        - Battmann, J. L.
          - Mass in F, vocal and instrumental parts (Box 24)
        - Beethoven, Ludwig van
          - Mass in C, organ score (Box 24)
          - Kyrie from Op. 27, vocal score (Box 24)
        - Bordese, Luigi
          - Mass [in G minor]; Kyrie (Box 24)
          - Mass [in G minor], vocal parts, with addl. voices by Bissell and Newland (Box 24)
        - Bühler, F.
          - Mass No. 1 in E-flat, vocal score, organ/vocal score, vocal parts (Box 25)
          - Missa brevis in F, No. 2 (Box 25)
          - Missa brevis in A, No. 3, vocal score (Box 25)
          - Benedictus, solo bass part (Box 25)
        - Carr, Benjamin
          - Mass; Sanctus, Agnus Dei see: Lederer, Mass in D, Box 26
        - Cimarosa, Domenico
          - Kyrie, organ/vocal score (Box 25)
        - Concone, Joseph
          - Mass [in F], basso part (Box 25)
        - Daunas, Pedro
          - Missa Espagnole, organ score with text (Box 25)
          - Missa Pastorelle pour la Nuit de Noël, organ score with text (Box 25)
        - Monti de Rezé, Edouard de
          - Mass [in B-flat]; Alto added by W. A. Newland, alto part (Box 25)
        - Dielman, H.
          - Mass for Two Tenors & Bass [in F]; Kyrie, Gloria, organ score with text (Box 25)
          - Mass [in C]; Kyrie Eleison [in C], organ/vocal score; vocal score (Box 25)
        - Dietsch, Pierre-Louis-Philippe
          - Mass in B-flat, organ score with text (Box 25)
        - Dos Santos, A. F.
          - Mass in G for 3 voices, organ/vocal score (Box 25)
        - Emmerig, W. J.
          - Missa Solemnis in D. Organ accompaniment by W. A. Newland, organ/vocal score (Box 25)
        - Farmer, Henry
          - Mass in B-flat, vocal parts, organ score with text (Box 25)
        - Feltz, L.
          - Mass in E-flat, soprano part (Box 26)
        - Generalis
          - Mass in G, violin part (Box 26)
        - Gounod, Charles
          - Messe Solennelle (St. Cecilia), organ score with text; Edition: Boosey edition (Box 26)
          - 2d Messe à 4 voci per tenori e bassi, part for bassi I and II (Box 26)
          - [Unidentified], Mass fragment, vocal score (Box 26)
        - Hachs, T. von
          - Missa pro pace, solo violin part, organ score with text (Box 26)
        - Haydn, Franz Joseph
          - Mass in B-flat, No. 1, V. 1 and Va. parts; Includes: O Jesu Deus, by Haydn Jesu Dei vivi, Terzetto from Atella, by Verdi Ave Maris Stella, by Donizetti O Salutaris Hostia, by Bishop Mihi Jesu Mellifluus, by F. Schneider Jesu Filii Dei, Terzettino by Winter O Jesu Jesu, by Mozart Ave Maria, by Cherubini and O Salutaris, by Cherubini (Box 26)
          - Mass in C, No. 2, string parts (Box 26)
          - Mass in C, No. 2. Organ accompaniment by W. A. Newland, 2 copies; 1 copy also includes: Alleluja Chorus from Mount of Olives by Beethoven (Box 26)
          - Mass in D, No. 3. Organ accompaniment by W. A. Newland, organ score with text; Includes: Novello's simplified versions of Kyrie and Dona Nobis in Appendix Haydn and Mozart Te Deums with organ accompaniment by W. A. Newland (Box 26)
          - Mass No. 4. Organ accompaniment by W. A. Newland, 1854, organ score with text; also includes: Mass [in B-flat] No. 16 (Box 26)
        - Haydn, Michael
          - Missa Solemnis in C, violin part (Box 26)
        - Heuberer, Charles F.
          - Mass [in G], also: alto vocal score (Box 26)
        - Hummel, Johann Nepomuk
          - Messe Solenne in E-flat, organ score with text (Box 27)
        - Jordan, Rev. P.
          - Mass for Children; Kyrie, vocal part (Box 27)
          - Requiem (Box 27)
        - Kalliwoda, J. W.
          - Mass in A, op. 137, organ score with text (Box 27)
          - Mass [in A], op. 137 see: Weber, Mass in G, Box 29
        - Krommer, Franz
          - Missa Solemnis in C, op. 108. Organ accompaniment by W. A. Newland, organ/vocal score (Box 27)
        - Kuhn
          - Messe Solennelle. Organ accompaniment by W. A. Newland, organ/vocal score (Box 27)
        - Lambillotte, Louis
          - Pascale Mass, organ score with text (Box 27)
        - Lederer, Joseph
          - Mass No. 1 (1781), vocal parts (Box 27)
          - Mass No. 2 (1781), vocal parts (Box 27)
          - Mass No. 3, in G, organ score with text (Box 27)
          - Mass [in D]; Gloria, Sanctus, Agnus Dei, vocal score; Includes: Sanctus and Agnus Dei from Mass by Carr Ave Maria by Zingarelli (Box 27)
          - Six Masses. Organ accompaniment by W. A. Newland, organ/vocal score; 2 copies (Box 27)
          - Et in Spiritum Sanctum [from Masses No. 2,4,5,6], organ score with text (Box 27)
        - Lejeal, Alois F.
          - Mass in D, vocal and instrumental parts (Box 27)
          - Mass see: Weber, Mass in G, Box 29
        - Mazzinghi, Joseph
          - Mass, arr. for 4 voices by W. A. Newland, 1862, alto part, organ score with text; Alto part by W. A. Newland (Box 27)
        - Meignen, Leopold
          - Missa Solemnis, vocal score, organ score with text, organ/vocal score (Box 28)
        - Mercadente, Saverio
          - Mass in A [transposed from B-flat], organ score with text (Box 28)
          - Mass in B-flat. Alto part by W. A. Newland, 1862 (Box 28)
          - Mass see: Millard, Vespers, Box 30
        - Millard, Harrison
          - Mass in G, No. 1, organ score with text; 2 copies (Box 28)
        - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus
          - [Mass in G]. Organ accompaniment by W. A. Newland, 1845, organ score with text (Box 28)
          - Mass in B-flat, No. 7, vocal parts (Box 28)
          - Mass No. 12, violin solo; Includes violin parts for: March Romain and March Jubilato, by Hummel Wedding March, by J. R. Fairlamb: Domine Deus from Mass by Rossini St. John the Baptist, by Charles Zeuner, arranged by William Newland (Box 28)
          - Mass No. 12, title page, violin part (Box 28)
        - Natividad
          - Mass, arr. for 4 voices [by W. A. Newland], tenor part (Box 28)
        - Newland, William Augustine
          - Mass No. 2, vocal and instrumental parts (Box 28)
          - Missa Brevis No. I, vocal and instrumental parts (Box 28)
          - Missa Pastorale in C, 1858 (Box 28)
        - Novello, Vincent
          - Mass in E for 2 voices, with ad lib tenor by W. A. Newland, 1853, vocal parts (Box 29)
        - Raffelin, A.
          - Missa brevis in G., with additional tenor by W. A. Newland (Box 29)
        - Rossini, Gioacchino
          - Domine Deus see: Mozart, Mass No. 12, Box 28
          - Sanctus [and] Agnus Dei, vocal parts (Box 29)
        - Ruitzy
          - Mass Pastorale, organ score with text (Box 29)
        - St. Clair, C. G.
          - Mass in G, organ/vocal score, organ score with text (Box 29)
        - Schubert, Franz
          - Mass in F, organ/vocal score (Box 29)
        - Vogler, Georg Joseph
          - Missa Pastorale No. 2 in E, organ/vocal score (Box 29)
          - Missa Pastoritia, No. 2 in D. Organ accompaniment by W. A. Newland, organ score with text; transposition of Missa Pastorale in E (Box 29)
          - Missa Solemnis No. I. Organ accompaniment by W. A. Newland, organ score with text (Box 29)
        - Webbe, Samuel
          - Mass in A; Kyrie, Gloria, organ score with text (Box 29)
        - Weber, Carl Maria von
          - Mass. Organ accompaniment by W. A. Newland, organ score with text (Box 29)
          - Mass in G, violin obbligato; Includes: Mass by Le Jeal Mass by J. W. Kalliwoda, op. 137 (Box 29)
        - Zimmer
          - Mass No. 2 in B-flat., organ/vocal score; Arranged for the organ by W. A. Newland (Box 29)
          - Missa Brevis, organ score with text (Box 29)
      - Title only (Box 29)
        - Mass No. 3, organ/vocal score (Box 29)
        - Sanctus, organ/vocal score, vocal parts (Box 29)
        - [Mass responses] (Box 29)
        - [Miscellaneous vocal fragments] (Box 29)
    - Requiem Masses and Fragments - Printed music (Box 31)
      - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus
        - Requiem à quatre voix see: Pergolesi, Stabat Mater, Box 31
    - Requiem Masses and Fragments - Manuscripts (Box 30)
      - By Composer (Box 30)
        - Desvignes, P.
          - Pie Jesu, organ score with text (Box 30)
        - Jordan, Rev. P.
          - [Requiem Mass], vocal score with incipits only (Box 30)
        - Ohnewald, J.
          - [Requiem Mass] No. 2 in B-flat, vocal score (Box 30)
        - Tomaschek, W. J.
          - [Requiem Mass], vocal scores, nos. I-IV (Box 30)
          - Messa Cantata con piena Orchestra - Fatta in Venezia see also: for orchestral score, Box 4, organ/vocal score; includes requiem texts (Box 30)
      - Title only (Box 30)
        - [Requiem fragments] (Box 30)
    - Vespers services and excerpts - Printed music (Box 30)
      - W. A. Newland's collection of Vespers. Philadelphia: W. A. Newland, n.d., Published and for sale by W. A. Newland.; 10 sets; Includes cover pages for: Catholic Church Music. Masses, Vespers & Responses. Boston: Ditson & Co. Catholic Church Music, Seventh Series - Peters Collection. New York: J. L. Peters Catholic Church Music, Ninth Series. Boston: Ditson & Co. (Box 30)
      - W. A. Newland's collection of Sacred Music, Nos. 1-10. Philadelphia: W. A. Newland, 1850., Published and for sale by W. A. Newland; Contains works by B. Carr, W. Newland, J. Ohnewald, Paxton, and R. Taylor (Box 30)
    - Vespers services and excerpts - Manuscripts (Box 30)
      - By Composer (Box 30)
        - Este
          - [Unidentified], vocal parts (Box 30)
        - Millard, Harrison
          - [Unidentified], organ score with text; Includes: Magnificats and Vespers by Marzo and Mercadente Mass by Mercadente (Box 30)
        - Newland, William Augustine
          - [Unidentified], 6 sets of vocal parts (Box 30)
        - Rosewig, Albert H.
          - [Unidentified], organ score with text (Box 30)
        - Scherbauer, K.
          - Vesperae breves (Op. 5), vocal parts (Box 30)
      - Title only (Box 30)
        - [Vespers fragments] (Box 30)
    - Motets, anthems, antiphons, etc. - Printed music (Box 31)
      - By Composer (Box 31)
        - André, Anton
          - Te Deum Laudamus komponirt und in einen Klavier-Auszug gebracht von Anton André. 60stes Werk. Offenbach a/M: Johann André, [1829-1833]., Pl. no. 5250. (Box 31)
        - Fuss, Johann
          - Hymnus. Johann Fuss in Wien. (Beylage zur allgemeinen musikalischen Zeitung, [No. 51]; No. 9). (Box 31)
        - Gounod, Charles
          - Ave Maria by Charles Gounod. [S.l.]: N. & P., n.d., Popular soprano or tenor songs (Box 31)
        - Handel, George Frideric
          - Te Deum [Laudamus] in Score Composed for His Grace the Duke of Chandos in the Year 1720 by G. F. Handel. No. 20. (Box 31)
        - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus
          - Te Deum a 4 Voci coll accompagnamento di due Violini, Bassi e Organo composto da W. A. Mozart. Partitura mit unterlegtem deutschen Texte von C. A. H. Clodius. Leipzig: Breitkopf und Härtel, [1803]., Inscribed on title page: C. F. Abel (Box 31)
        - Neukomm, Sigismund Ritter von
          - Hymnus für drey Stimmen, von Hrn Ritter S. von Neukomm. (Beilage zur allgem. musikal. Zeitung 1825. No. 40; No. III). (Box 31)
        - Pergolesi, Giovanni Battista
          - Stabat [Mater] de Pergolèse. A deux voix avec accompagnement de Piano ou Orgue. Édition deluxe. Paris: V. Launer, n.d., Pl. no. Vve. L.3335.; also includes: Requiem à quatre voix, by Mozart (Box 31)
        - Raffelin, A.
          - [Ave verum corpus] A. Raffelin. Partitur. Offenbach s/M: Joh. André, n.d. (Box 31)
        - Webbe, Samuel
          - Tantum Ergo, No. 3, also includes Tantum Ergo no. 4, by Fr. X. Schmid (Box 31)
        - Winter, Peter
          - Ave Maria. Trio. For the Offertory. Music by Winter. Cincinnati: W. C. Peters & Sons, n.d., from The Musical World and Times (Box 31)
          - Regina Coeli. Trio [for] Two Trebles and Tenor. Arranged from Winter. (Box 31)
        - Winter, Peter and Vincent Novello
          - Jesu Fili Dei. Terzettino for Benediction from Winter and Novello. Cincinnati: W. C. Peters & Sons, n.d., Pl. no. 1124; Manuscript alteration. both to score and to manuscript solo bass part (Box 31)
      - Title only (Box 31)
        - Magnificat - Canticum B. V. M. (Box 31)
    - Motets, anthems, antiphones, etc. - Manuscripts (Box 31-35)
      - Adeste Fideles (Box 31)
        - Novello, Vincent (arranger)
          - Adeste Fideles, organ score with text (Box 31)
      - Adoremus Natum (Box 31)
        - Souvin, Edward
          - Adoremus Natum, organ score with text (Box 31)
      - Alma Redemptoris Mater (Box 31)
        - Bordese, Luigi
          - Alma Redemptoris Mater, soprano part (Box 31)
        - Lutgen, Paul
          - Alma Redemptoris Mater, organ score with text (Box 31)
      - Amor Jesu (Box 31)
        - Neukomm, Sigismund Ritter von
          - Amor Jesu, vocal score (Box 31)
      - Asperges (Box 31)
        - Novello, Vincent
          - Asperges, bassi part; [on verso] Asperges from Catholic Choir, p. 18 (Box 31)
        - Werner, A.
          - Asperges, [on] Domine from Garbet vocal parts (Box 31)
        - [Unidentified]
          - Asperges, [in] Inchoat Sacerdos Antiphonam [rubric] (Box 31)
      - Ave Maria (Box 31)
        - Cherubini, Luigi
          - Ave Maria see: Haydn, Mass in B-flat, Box 26
        - Luzzi, Luigi
          - Ave Maria, cornet part, organ/vocal score (2 copies); English version by H. Millard; Includes: Ave Maria by Rossini from Seperazione (Peters 4115) Duo from Stabat [Mater] by Rossini (Box 31)
        - Mascagni
          - Ave Maria, [from] Cavalleria Rusticana.; Arranged by W. A. Newland; Includes: O Salutaris by W. F. Pecher, organist of New York Cathedral. Arranged by W. A. Newland Jesu, Jesu by Mozart, Bass solo with chorus. Arranged by W. A. Newland (Box 31)
        - Rossini, Gioacchino
          - Ave Maria see: Ave Maria by Luzzi (above)
        - Schubert, Franz
          - Ave Maria, organ score with text (Box 31)
        - [Unidentified]
          - Ave Maria (Box 31)
      - Ave maris stella (Box 32)
        - Donizetti, Gaetano
          - Ave maris stella see: Haydn, Mass in B-flat, Box 26
        - Thomas, J. B.
          - Ave maris stella, soprano part (Box 32)
      - Ave Regina (Box 32)
        - Raffelin, A.
          - Ave Regina, solo soprano (or tenor) with organ (Box 32)
      - Ave Verum (Box 32)
        - [Unidentified]
          - Ave Verum (Box 32)
      - Beata es virgo (Box 32)
        - Est, L. B.
          - Beata es virgo, organ/vocal score (Box 32)
      - Bone Pastor (Box 32)
        - Rossini, Gioacchino